The police in Decatur, Alabama shot a father of two for his truck at his own home and the amount
of effort that the local media is using to lie about the shit to cover it up is like, it's amazing
to me. We are learning new details this half hour after an officer involved shooting in Decatur
early this morning. A spokesperson with Decatur police tells News 19 officers shot a suspect
on Ryan Drive early this morning after responding to a call by a local towing company. DPD says the
towing company was attempting to repossess a vehicle in the 3900 block of Ryan Drive when
the homeowner pulled a gun on the tow truck driver. When officers arrived on scene, police
say they ordered the suspect to drop his weapon, but instead he turned the gun on police.
This is the security camera from Steven Perkins. How much you want to bet if I zoom this in,
not only do we find out is he unarmed with just a flashlight, but he has his hands raised.
To stay within CG guidelines, I'm going to stop this video right before Steven gets dropped
by seven of the 13 bullets fired by three different officers, two of which were hiding in the dark
by the way. But other than the fact that he has his hands up the entire time armed with
only a flashlight, you should also know that his car was not delinquent.
By the way, a Perkins family statement also claims they have car payment receipts to prove
that the tow truck and Decatur police were at the wrong home tonight.
I was amazed at how the local media in real fucking time constantly changed their story to cover up for
the police in Alabama. It was like, oh, they were trying to repo his car. Oh, he pointed a gun at them.
Like any third grader with a phone couldn't zoom in on the surveillance footage to clearly see his
hands are up. Oh, and by the way, I think it's real funny that the auto detection on the security
cams didn't catch the tow truck driver showing up the first time around. Oh, but when the cops showed
up, all of a sudden it turned on. Wait, if the department really wanted to gain the trust of the
community, they could just release the body camera footage and the audio from the dispatch.
Because, you know, if there really was a gun in the area, they would have gotten a call for it.
I mean, why else would three cops show up at some random dude's home?
In a statement tonight released by a Perkins family member reads in part, it is heartbreaking
for his wife, children, and family to go through this traumatizing loss without much detail or
explanation. It goes on to say that neither the city of Decatur or the state bureau of investigation
has contacted the family. They say this was excessive force, saying he was shot seven times.
Yeah, why would the cops call the family to somebody they just did a hit job on? At best,
they showed up at the wrong house, and at worst, I don't fucking know. He has a GoFundMe. I put in 100.
Do whatever you want.